**Summer is here, and so is the sale. Get a yearly plan with up to 65% off today! 🌴🌞**

* Solutions

* Templates
* Integrations
    
    [
    
    Slack](https://forms.app/en/integrations/slack)
    
    [
    
    HubSpot CRM](https://forms.app/en/integrations/hubspot-crm)
    
    [
    
    Google Sheets](https://forms.app/en/integrations/google-sheets)
    
    [
    
    Trello](https://forms.app/en/integrations/trello)
    
    [
    
    Google Analytics](https://forms.app/en/integrations/google-analytics)
    
    [
    
    Microsoft Excel](https://forms.app/en/integrations/microsoft-excel)
    
    [
    
    Notion](https://forms.app/en/integrations/notion)
    
    [
    
    Airtable](https://forms.app/en/integrations/airtable)

* Resources

Try without registration [Quick Start](https://forms.app/myforms?create=true)

[

Blog

Read engaging stories, how-to guides, learn about forms.app features.](https://forms.app/en/blog)

[

Templates

Inspirational ready-to-use templates for getting started fast and powerful.](https://forms.app/en/templates)

[

Help Center

Spot-on guides on how to use forms.app and make the most out of it.](https://forms.app/en/help-center)

[

Security

See the technical measures we take and learn how we keep your data safe and secure.](https://forms.app/en/security)

Privacy Policy
==============

* **Privacy Policy**

**Keep your data protected with powerful security features of forms.app. Learn more about which technologies we use to protect your data.**

1- Introduction
---------------

Forms.app is an online form builder that you can collect data of any size. We believe that everyone has a right of privacy. We view privacy as a key part of the value that we deliver to our customers.

This privacy policy explains how forms.app uses and processes your personal data and applies to all the products, services and websites offered by FORMS APP OÜ which is based in the EU. Products, apps, services and websites are collectively referred to as the “Services” in this policy.

2- Information we collect
-------------------------

### 2.1. Form creators

#### a. Registration information

We collect information about you when you register for an account through the Services. You provide your name and surname, email address and username when you register for the Services. You also have the option to register by using some third-party accounts(such as Google, Facebook, Apple or Stack Overflow) If you choose to register by using a third party account please see “Information from third parties” below.

#### b. Account Preferences

You have the option of adding a profile photo and team members. Also you can prefer the language, timezone and district to specify your date, number and time view to be displayed in our Services. We keep track of your preferences when you select settings within the Services.

#### c. Billing information

If you make a payment to Forms App OÜ and provide your billing details, we store your name, address, email address and tax number information. If you provide a billing address, we will regard that as the location of the account holder to determine Forms App OÜ entity with whom you contract and the sales tax. Our integrations with third party payment gateways are processing your financial information only. We don’t store or log any sensitive cardholder or credit card number data provided by you or your responders.

#### d. Form questions and responses

We store your form questions and responses by using third-party server providers such as Google Cloud for you and provide analysis tools for you to use with respect to this data.We treat your forms as private, unless you make them available to members of the public. We don’t sell or share your forms or responses you collect. Never use your forms or responses for purposes unrelated to you or our services however Forms App OÜ is compelled by a subpoena or court order, or if you’ve given us permission to do so.

### 2.2. Responders

#### a. If you respond anonymous

Form creators can collect responses anonymously on Services. However, even if a form creator collects responses anonymously, specific questions in the form may still ask you for your personal information or data that could be used to identify you. We store your responses on behalf of the creator even if you respond anonymously and we are not responsible for the content of that form. The creator may have their own privacy policy and please contact the creator directly.

#### b. If you sign up forms.app to respond to the form

If you have to sign up forms.app to respond to the form, we collect your registration information. Please check out Form Creators heading in this policy. We store your responses on behalf of the creator and we are not responsible for the content of that form. The creator may have their own privacy policy and please contact the creator directly.

### 2.3. Visitors

#### a. Usage information

We collect usage information about visitors whenever they interact with our websites and services. This includes which webpages visitors visit, what they click on, when they perform those actions, what language preference they have and so on.

#### b. Contact information

If any visitor of Services contacts us and provides us with contact information whether through use of Services, a form on our website, an interaction with our customer support team, or a response to one of creators we collect and store contact information for purposes related to your contact purpose.

#### c. Device and browser data

We collect information from the device and application you use to access Services. Device data mainly means your IP address, forms.app user ID(not valid for anonymous responses), operating system name, operating system version, device model, device type, device brand name, browser name and version. We may also infer your location information based on your IP address.

#### d. Information from page tags

We use commonly used tools such as cookies, web beacons, pixels, local shared objects and similar technologies (collectively "cookies") to collect information about you so we can provide the experiences you request, recognize your visit, track your interactions, and improve your and other customers' experience. You have control over some of the information we collect from Cookies and how we use it. For full details on how we use cookies and similar technologies please see our **[Cookie Policy.](https://forms.app/en/cookie-policy)**

#### e. Referral information

If you visit our website from an external source (such as a link on another website or in an email), we record information about the source that referred you to us.

### 2.4. Information from third parties

We collect your personal information from third parties, where you give permission to those third parties to share your information with us, where such information is publicly available online or through your device/browser data. forms.app also collects information through authentications when you connect it with other applications. We do not use Google Workplace APIs to develop, improve, or train generalized AI and/or ML models.

3- How we use the information we collect
----------------------------------------

**We collect and process the information about you where:**

* We have your consent to do so;
* We have a contract with you and it is necessary to process your personal information to perform our contract with you, including to provide you with the benefits of Service and operate our business;
* The processing is in our legitimate business interests (in those jurisdictions where legitimate business interest is a legitimate basis for processing) such as operating our businesses, improving and developing Services, communicating with you, marketing our offerings and services and personalizing your experience, and to detect illegal activities;
* We need to comply with legal requirements, including applicable laws and regulations.

**The information is used for the following purposes including to:**

* Provide you with Services, create your account and manage our relationship with you,
* Improve and develop our products and services by analyzing how you are used and interacted with, as well as by assessing the use of and interactions with our Services and certain content our customers send or display through the Services, including by conducting data analytics to develop insights about you, your needs and preferences so we can make more informed predictions, recommendations and products for our customers,
* Run and manage our business, including resolving billing and financial disputes,
* Evaluate your eligibility for financial or other marketing offers, products and services,
* Provide features to you, such as your reports and quota,
* Connect you with other users to organize a team,
* Communicate with you, such as sending you electronic notifications concerning your financial privacy,
* Protect against misuse or abuse of our services and ensure compliance with our terms, including in relation to content our customers send or display through Services,
* Market our services, products and experiences, including to deliver gifts and promotional materials, product recommendations and other non-transactional communications via email or push notifications, in accordance with your marketing preferences,
* Personalize your experience and tailor recommendations, advertising and offers presented to you, including through the development of insights about you and your needs based on your interactions with the products, services and offerings of Service,
* Combine and anonymize information about your interactions with Service to create aggregate, anonymized statistics for use in research and for marketing, promoting, improving and developing our platform,
* Provide you with support and resolve disputes,
* Conduct research, including by partnering with academic institutions,
* Comply with our legal and regulatory requirements,
* Manage event registrations and attendance, including sending related communications to you,
* Protect the rights, property, safety or security of Services, our customers, employees or others and prevent fraudulent or illegal activity,
* Exercise our rights in the course of judicial, administrative or arbitration proceedings,
* Enforce, remedy or apply our [**Terms of Use**](https://forms.app/en/terms) or other agreements and/or
* Process your information for other purposes that are compatible with the disclosed purposes if and where this is permitted by applicable law.

4- Information we share
-----------------------

**We may share your information in the following circumstances:**

* We use service providers who help us to provide you with Services. We give some personnel of these providers access to your information, but only to the extent necessary for them to perform their services for us. Our contracts with our service provider require them to maintain technical protections to ensure the confidentiality of your personal information and data, to use it only for the provision of their services to us, and to handle it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Examples of service providers include cloud services, payment processors, hosting services, email service providers, and web traffic analytic tools.
* If your account holder details are different from the billing contact listed for your account, we may disclose your identity and account details to the billing contact upon their request. We typically will attempt to notify you of such requests. By using our services and agreeing to this Privacy Policy, you consent to this disclosure.
* If the email address under which you’ve registered your account belongs to or is controlled by an organization, we may disclose that email address to that organization in order to help it understand who associated with that organization uses our services, and to assist the organization with its enterprise accounts.
* We aggregate or anonymize information to third parties to improve or promote Services so that no individuals can reasonably be identified or linked to any part of the information we share with third parties to improve or promote our services.
* We may ask advertising networks and exchanges to display ads promoting our services on other websites. We may ask such parties to deliver those ads based on the presence of a cookie that was placed when you visited one of our websites, but in doing so we will not share any other personal information with the advertiser. Our advertising network partners may also use cookies and page tags or web beacons to collect certain non-personal information about your activities on this and other websites to provide you with targeted advertising based upon your interests.
* We may disclose your information as required or permitted by law, or when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, subpoena, or other legal process served on us.
* If ownership of all or substantially all of our business changes, or we undertake a corporate reorganization, including a merger, acquisition or consolidation or any other action or transfer between forms.app entities, you expressly consent to Forms App OÜ transferring your information to the new owner or successor entity so that we can continue providing our services.
* We may expressly request your consent to provide your contact details to third parties for various purposes, including to allow those third parties to contact you for marketing purposes. If you give your consent, you may later revoke your permission, but if you wish to stop receiving communications from a third party to which we provided your information with your permission, you will need to contact that third party directly.

6- Security
-----------

We use physical, technical and organizational safeguards designed to protect your information. You can find out more about how we protect your information **[here.](https://forms.app/en/security)**

7- Your rights
--------------

Either if you are a creator, a visitor, a professional, or a third party, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. You also have the right to request access to, and rectification of, or erasure of your personal information, or restriction of processing, or to object to processing, as well as the right to data portability(applicable only when we use your personal information on the basis of your consent or performance of a contract, and where our use of your information is carried out by automated means). Please ask us to consider any valid objections which you have to our use of your personal information where we process it one the basis of our or another person’s letimigate interest. You can request via this [**form**](https://my.forms.app/forms/your-privacy-rights)**.**

We will consider all such requests and provide our response within a reasonable period (but no longer than one calendar month from our receipt of your request unless we tell you we are entitled to a longer period under applicable law). We may require you to verify your identity before we respond to any of your requests. Certain personal information may be exempt from such requests in certain circumstances, including as provided for in this Policy.

**Data retention policy:** Once a user becomes inactive, the user’s data is retained for 12 month. All the data gets automatically deleted after 12 month unless the user becomes active within this period.

**Data removal policy:** A forms.app user can request deletion of his/her data at any time. If you want to delete your forms.app account please fill in this [form](https://my.forms.app/form/6287af5040535c37d67c0cfd). Please note that if you choose to delete your account and request for data deletion, your account will be deleted after 30 days of your request and all data in your account will be permanently removed from our systems.

If you are a California consumer you can find out more about your rights **[here.](https://forms.app/en/help-center/ccpa-compliance)**

If you are an Australia resident or resident of the UK or EEA(Europe Economic Area) you can find out more about your rights **[here.](https://forms.app/en/help-center/privacy-notice-for-australia-uk-and-eea-citizens)**

Services are not intended for and may not be used by minors. “Minors” are individuals under the age of 13 (or under a higher age if permitted by the laws of their residence). Forms App OÜ does not knowingly collect personal data from Minors or allow them to register. If it comes to our attention that we have collected personal data from a Minor, we may delete this information without notice. If you have reason to believe that this has occurred, please contact customer support.

8-Contact us
------------

If you have any questions about Policy, you may contact us using this [**form**](https://my.forms.app/forms/your-privacy-rights)**.** You can also contact us via **[\[email protected\]](https://forms.app/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)**

**Last updated on July 2024**

#### Power your next form with forms.app

[GET STARTED](https://forms.app/myforms)forms.app is free to use. We also offer paid plans with  
storage and support.

**Solutions**

**Templates**

**Integrations**

**Helpful Comparisons**

**Resources**

**Contact Us**

English

* [
    
    App Store Page Logo](https://apps.apple.com/us/app/forms-app/id1477890863)
* [
    
    Google Play Store Page Logo](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.formsapp&hl=en)
* [
    
    Huawei Appgallery Page Logo](https://appgallery.huawei.com/#/app/C104075803)

###### © 2024 forms.app. All rights reserved.
